Balinese Tari Legong dancers, Indonesia
Kilauea Volcano, Hawaii
Museum of Egyptian Antiquites
Popa Taungkalat Monastery, Bagan Myanmar
Bagan, Myanmar
Thiksey Monastery, Leh Ladakh India
Mt. Nemrut National Park, Adiyaman, Turkey
Petra,Jordan
Cappadocia,Turkey
Dogon Village, Bandiagara Escarpment Cliff
dwellings near terelli, Mali
Kolmanskop Namibia
Katrina House, Ninth Ward, New Orleans
Ninth Ward, New Orleans
Chateau de Versailles, France
Divino, Salvador Church, Sao Paulo Brazil
Cathedral de Notre Dame de Reims
Cathedral Notre Dame de Paris
Convento dei Cappuccini, Palermo
La Sainte Chapelle
Mont Saint Michel
Naukluft National Park,
Sossusvlei, Namibia
Ron Mt. Blanc, France
Arches National Park, Utah USA
Monument Valley, Arizona USA
Antelope Canyon
Epupa Falls, Angola
Omo, Mursi
Mursi tribes, Omo Valley, Ethiopia
Himba village, Kunene Namibia
Marcos Luna
tattoo daddy, America
Hiroshi Ishiguro
Professor and Robot Clone, Japan
Oloiver de Sagazan, Paris
Toshimaen/Hydropolis,tokyo
Lotte Kasai Golf, Chiba
Ski Dubai
Burj Khalifa Tower
Burj Al Arab Hotel
Galleria Vittorio Emanuele
Milan, Italy
Teatro alla Scala, Italy
Aadlen bros. Auto wrecking, Sun valley
Electronic Recyclers International, Fresno
Costco, Van Nuys
Tsuchiya Shokai Doll Factory, Japan
Ladyboy, Cascade go-go bar,
Nana Plaza, Bangkok
Fushimi Inari Shrine, Kyoto
Kikumaru Geisha, Japan
Cebu Province Detention and Rehabilitation Center,
Cebu City, Philippines
Payatas Trash Dump, Quezon city
Kawah Ijen Sulfur Mine,
Java, Indonesia
Kane Kwei Coffin Shop,
Accra, Ghana
Arms corporation of the Philippines
Omo Mursi
Mursi tribes, Omo Valley, Ethiopia
Staff sergeant Robert Henline
US Army veteran, Los Angeles National Cemetery
Tagou Wushu Academy,
Zhengzhou, China
Demilitarized zone, Panmunjom
Wailing wall,
Jerusalem
Great Mosque of Djenne, Mali
Great Pyramids of Giza, Egypt
Mosque of Sultanahmet,
Istanbul Turkey
al-Masjid Al-Haram,
Mecca Saudi Arabia
Thiksey Monastery,
Leh, Ladakh, India
Beijing